New England Hospital for Women and Children Records, 1792-1994
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES VI. AUTOGRAPH COLLECTION 1792-1905, 2 linear ft.
  - Letters
    - Parsons, Theophilis, 1884-88, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Paul, C. Kegan, 1884 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Peacock, H.B., undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Peabody, Andrew Preston, 1852-79 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Peabody, Elizabeth Palmer, 1881-87, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Peabody, Lucia, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Pennington, K. M., undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Perkins, Charles C., undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Phelps, Elizabeth Stuart, 1889 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Phillips, Adelaide, undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Phillips, Wendell, 1843-78, undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Pickersgill, Fred R., undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Pierce, Edward L., 1879-82 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Pillsbury, Parker, 1884 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Pitman, Henry A., 1884 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Porter, Leslie, 1887 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Porter, Maria S., undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Potter, Thomas B., 1863 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Potter, William J., 1867-85 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Powell, Aaron M., 1887 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Pratt, Anna (Alcott), undated (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Prescott, William W., undated (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Purvis, Robert, 1857 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Putnam, Elizabeth C., 1856 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Putnam, Herbert, 1897 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Putnam, M., undated (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Quincy, Edmund, 1870 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Quincy, Josiah, 1863 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Ramabai, Saravasti, 1887 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Read, Thomas Buchanan, undated (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Reade, Charles, undated (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Redpath, James, 1875 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Reed, Helen L., undated (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Reid, Whitelaw, 1865 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Rhys, Ernest, 1888, undated (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Richards, Ellen Swallow, 1892-94, undated (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Rideing, William H., 1890 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Rimmer, Caroline Hunt, 1880, undated (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Rimmer, W.T., 1870 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Rimmer, William, 1861?,1864 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Robinson, Charles S., undated (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Robinson, J. T., 1891 (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Robinson, John, 1873 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Rogers, Seth, 1887 (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1900? (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - Roscoe, Henry, 1895 (Box 25, Folder 68)
    - Rossetti, Christina, 1889, undated (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - Rossetti, William M., 1890 (Box 25, Folder 70)
    - Roy, Pratopa Chandra, 1886-87 (Box 25, Folder 71)
    - Ruggles-Kitson, Theodore, undated (Box 25, Folder 72)
    - Runkle, John Daniel, 1889 (Box 25, Folder 73)
    - Russell, E. H., 1883 (Box 25, Folder 74)
    - Russell, Thomas, undated (Box 25, Folder 75)
    - Sainsbury, J., 1856 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Salt, H.S., undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Sanborn, Benjamin Franklin, 1888-89 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Schindler, Solomon, 1888 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Schoff, S.A., 1886-97 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Schurz, Carl, 1866 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Scollard, Clinton, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Scott, William B., 1877-78 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Scudder, Horace Elisha, 1872, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Scudder, Vida, 1887, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Seeley, J.R., 1911? (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Sewell, H.E, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Sewell, H.W., undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Seward, William H., 1834? (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Sharp, William, 1881, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Sherman, William Tecumseh, 1881 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Shields, Frederick J., 1881 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Shippen, Rush R., 1888 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Sievers, E., 1887 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Simmons, Franklin, 1867 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Simpson, Joseph, 1861? (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Julia Holmes, 1886 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Smith, M. A., 1880 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Smith, Sheldon?, undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Smith, Walter, 1872 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Somerset, Isabel, 1895 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Southwick, Algernon, 1890 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Sparks, Jared, undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Spencer, Anna, 1881-90 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Spring, Marcus, 1869 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Spurgeon, G.H., 1868 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady, 1897, undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Stearns, Frank P., 1892 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Stedman, Edmund Clarence, 1884 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Stephenson, J.H., 1863-64 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Stevenson, Hanna E., 1866, undated (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Stewart, Balfour, 1887 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Stodder, Charles, 1883? (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Stone, Lucy 1879-93, undated (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Storer, Frank H., undated (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Story, Joseph, 1823-34 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Stowe, Harriet Beecher, 1860s-70 s, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Strong, James, 1887 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Sumner, Charles, 1846-53, undated (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Swanwick, Anna, undated (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Talbot, Marion, 1886-93 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Taylor, Bayard, 1875 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Taylor, C.W., undated (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Taylor, Mentia, undated (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Tetlow, John, 1887-91, undated (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Thaxter, Celia, 1862-88 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Thomas, Edith M., 1887 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Thomas, Martha Carey, 1880-1905 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Thompson, George, 1846 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Ticknor, George, 1864 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Treat, S.B., 1874 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Tudor, Mrs. Fenno, 1868 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Tyler, Moses Coit, 1887 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Tyndall, John, 1878 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Vacca, circa 1820 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Van Daell, 1892, undated (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Venturi, Emilie, 1871 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Venturo, L., undated (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Villa, E., 1879 (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - Walker, Francis A., 1879 (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Walker, James, 1858 (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - Ward, Genevieve, 1879-94, undated (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Ward, A. S., 1895 (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - Ware, Mary C., 1879 (Box 26, Folder 69)
    - Ware, John Fothergill Waterhouse, 1869 (Box 26, Folder 70)
    - Ware, L.G., n. d. (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Warner, Charles Dudley, 1877-92 (Box 26, Folder 72)
    - Warren, W.F., 1882-98, n. d. (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Washburn, Emory, 1854 (Box 26, Folder 74)
    - Washington, Booker Taliaferio, 1891-99 (Box 26, Folder 75)
    - Washington, Margaret Murray, 1894-99 (Box 26, Folder 76)
    - Wasson, D.A., 1865-87, n. d. (Box 26, Folder 77)
    - Wasson, George S., 1887 (Box 26, Folder 78)
    - Waters, C.E. Clement, 1887 (Box 26, Folder 79)
    - Watson, Sereno, 1862?, 1888 (Box 26, Folder 80)
    - Watts, A.M., 1884, undated (Box 26, Folder 81)
    - Watts, Walter Theodore, 1879, undated (Box 26, Folder 82)
    - Wedderborn, David, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Weld, Angelina Grimke, [see Grimke, Angelina Emily]
    - Weld, Theodore, 1877, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Welling, James C., 1887 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Wells, Kate Gannett, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Wendt, Charles W., 1885 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Wesselhoeft, William P., 1871-77, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Whipple, Charles K., 1868-85 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Whipple, Henry Benjamin, 1886 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Whitaker, O.W., 1887 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Whitman, Sarah W., 1860, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Whitney, A. S., 1888 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Whitney, Adeline Dutton Train, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Whitney, Anne, 1873-92, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Whitney, William Dwight, 1878-83 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Whittier, John Greenleaf, 1862-90 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Wilcox, J. A., 1887 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Wilcox, Monson A., 1887 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Wilder, Marshal P., 1879-82 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Willard, Frances E., 1888 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Wilson, Henry, 1847-64 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Winslow, Rev. William C., 1889 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Winsor, Justin, 1872-84 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Winthrop, Robert C., 1862-94 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Wolcott, Roger, 1898-99, undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Woods, Leonard, 1858 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Woolley, Mary E., 1905 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Woolner, T., 1869 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Woolsey, Sarah, undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Wright, H.C., 1839 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Wyman, Lillie B.C., 1892 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Autographs
    - On cards and fragments (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - On documents (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - On short letters and postcards (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Catalogue of autographs, New England Hospital Fair, undated (Box 27, Folder 34)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Poster from the Boston Globe for Black History Month about Marie Mahoney, undated (Map-case Flat File)
  - Fund drive poster, 1916 (Map-case Flat File)